Hasmukh Shah

Front-End Developer

Phone: 8200899614

Address: Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

Website: https://hasmukh7s.github.io/has

mukh-Resume/

Email: hasmukhweb19@gmail.com

I've been working from 2+ year as a Frontend Developer. During that time I've been trained software platforms and systems. I have experience in HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Wordpress(Design), Jquery and Javascript. I am Passionate about implementing and launching new projects. Looking to start the career as Frontend Developer with a reputed firm driven by technology.

EXPERIENCES

OpensourceXpert InfoTech, Ahmedabad

February 2022 - March, 2024

Frontend Developer

- Expand features, refine code, and improve processes, producing smoother operations and enhancing user engagement.
- I've experience in responsive Design.
- Design web applications according to client briefs and modify designs to meet changes in client specifications.
- Designing dynamic and browser compatible pages using HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Jquery and Javascript.
- Collaborated with Developer to design, test and improve web products.
- Assisted in the training of new developers.
- Ensure efficient web development by supporting designers and app developers while resolving website performance issues.
- · Ability to write Effectively, clean, minimalistic, reusable code.
- Utilized Adobe Photoshop, XD and Figma for the production of web-optimized Images.
- Maintained accuracy and attention to detail throughout the creative and development process.
- Handled multiple projects simultaneously while ensuring all projects were completed within the deadline date.

TOPS Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Ahmedabad

March 2021 - December 2021

Web Developer

- Designing new logos
- Developing different website pages with the help of html5,css3,bootstrap and jQuery
- · Responsive website using Media Jquery

DESIGN & CODING

Coding Skill

HTML

CSS

Tailwind

Bootstrap

Wordpress (Design)

jQuery

Javascript React JS (Basic) **Design Skill** XD Photoshop Illustrator Figma ChatGPT **Skill Highlights** Web Development **Cross Browser Operability** Project management **Process Improvement Workflow Optimization User Requirements Gathering** Linkdin https://www.linkedin.com/in/hasmukh-shah-4999ba1b3/?originalSubdomain=in **Gujarat University** 2021 MA **Gujarat University** 2020 BA 2017 **GHSEB HSC** 2015 **GHSCE** SSC

CERTIFICATES

SOCIAL

ACCOUNT

EDUCATION

TOPS Technologies

(03/2021 - 12/2021)

Web Developer & Graphic Designer

LANGUAGES	
	English
	Gujarati
	Hindi
HOBBIES &	
INTERESTS	Programming
	Travelling
	Designing
	Internet surfing
	Cricket

DECLARATION

Painting

Reading books

I hereby certify that all the information provided here is correct to the best of my knowledge.